{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In what year did the manga \"Ping Pong\" begin serialization?", "correct_answer": "1996", "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2010", "2003"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Highschool of the Dead\", where did Komuro and Saeko establish to meet after the bus explosion?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Police Station", "incorrect_answers": ["The Center Mall", "Komuro's House", "On The Main Bridge"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the first episode of Yu-Gi-Oh: Duel Monsters, what book is Seto Kaiba seen reading at Domino High School?", "correct_answer": "Thus Spoke Zarathustra", "incorrect_answers": ["Beyond Good and Evil", "The Republic", "Meditations"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Medaka Kurokami from \"Medaka Box\" has what abnormality?", "correct_answer": "The End", "incorrect_answers": ["Perfection", "Sandbox", "Fairness"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of the following countries does \"JoJo's Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders\" not take place in?", "correct_answer": "Philippines", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Pakistan", "Egypt"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio produced \"Log Horizon\"?", "correct_answer": "Satelite", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Production I.G"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "What is the last line muttered in the anime film \"The End of Evangelion\"?", "correct_answer": "\"How disgusting.\"", "incorrect_answers": ["\"Idiot, I won't let you kill me!\"", "\"Nothing.\"", "\"Goddammit, Shinji.\""]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these anime have over 7,500 episodes?", "correct_answer": "Sazae-san", "incorrect_answers": ["Naruto", "One Piece", "Chibi Maruko-chan"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the Overlord Anime who was Cocytus made by?", "correct_answer": "Warrior Takemikazuchi", "incorrect_answers": ["Peroroncino", "Ulbert Alain Odle", "Bukubukuchagama"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Author of the manga Uzumaki?", "correct_answer": "Junji Ito", "incorrect_answers": ["\tNoboru Takahashi", "Akira Toriyama", "Masashi Kishimoto"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Director of the 1988 Anime film \"Grave of the Fireflies\"?", "correct_answer": "Isao Takahata", "incorrect_answers": ["Hayao Miyazaki", "Satoshi Kon", "Sunao Katabuchi"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"One Piece\", who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?", "correct_answer": "Edward \"Whitebeard\" Newgate", "incorrect_answers": ["Former Marine Fleet Admiral Sengoku", "Pirate King Gol D Roger", "Silvers Rayleigh"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Hunter x Hunter\", which of the following is NOT a type of Nen aura?", "correct_answer": "Restoration", "incorrect_answers": ["Emission", "Transmutation", "Specialization"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which one of these characters is from \"Legendz : Tale of the Dragon Kings\"?", "correct_answer": "Shiron", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack", "Axia", "Drum"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the anime, Full Metal Panic!, who is Kaname's best friend?", "correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa", "incorrect_answers": ["Melissa Mao", "Ren Mikihara", "Teletha \"Tessa\" Testarossa"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these names are not a character of JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?", "correct_answer": "JoJo Kikasu", "incorrect_answers": ["Jean-Pierre Polnareff", "George Joestar", "Risotto Nero"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"One Piece\", what does \"the Pirate King\" mean to the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates?", "correct_answer": "Freedom", "incorrect_answers": ["Promise", "Adventure", "Friendship"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio animated \"To Love-Ru\"?", "correct_answer": "Xebec", "incorrect_answers": ["Trigger", "Sunrise", "Kyoto Animation"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Author of the manga Monster Hunter Orage?", "correct_answer": "Hiro Mashima", "incorrect_answers": ["Shin Yamamoto", "Keiichi Hikami", "Hirohiko Araki"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the \"Dragon Ball\" franchise, what is the name of Goku's brother?", "correct_answer": "Raditz", "incorrect_answers": ["Gohan", "Vegeta", "Bardock"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio produced \"Log Horizon\"?", "correct_answer": "Satelite", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Production I.G"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"One Piece\", what does \"the Pirate King\" mean to the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates?", "correct_answer": "Freedom", "incorrect_answers": ["Promise", "Adventure", "Friendship"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the first episode of Yu-Gi-Oh: Duel Monsters, what book is Seto Kaiba seen reading at Domino High School?", "correct_answer": "Thus Spoke Zarathustra", "incorrect_answers": ["Beyond Good and Evil", "The Republic", "Meditations"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the Overlord Anime who was Cocytus made by?", "correct_answer": "Warrior Takemikazuchi", "incorrect_answers": ["Peroroncino", "Ulbert Alain Odle", "Bukubukuchagama"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"One Piece\", who is the girl who overcame her enslaved past and became an agent of an army to fight the corrupt government?", "correct_answer": "Koala", "incorrect_answers": ["Boa Hancock", "Nico Robin", "Emporio Ivankov "]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "\"Silhouette\", a song performed by the group 'KANA-BOON' is featured as the sixteenth opening of which anime?", "correct_answer": "Naruto: Shippūden", "incorrect_answers": ["One Piece", "Naruto", "Gurren Lagann"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In which manga did the \"404 Girl\" from 4chan originate from?", "correct_answer": "Yotsuba&!", "incorrect_answers": ["Azumanga Daioh", "Lucky Star", "Clover"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Akatsuki's subclass in \"Log Horizon\" is what?", "correct_answer": " Tracker", "incorrect_answers": ["Assassin", "Scribe", "Apprentice"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Hunter x Hunter\", which of the following is NOT a type of Nen aura?", "correct_answer": "Restoration", "incorrect_answers": ["Emission", "Transmutation", "Specialization"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Medaka Kurokami from \"Medaka Box\" has what abnormality?", "correct_answer": "The End", "incorrect_answers": ["Perfection", "Sandbox", "Fairness"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Director of the 1988 Anime film \"Grave of the Fireflies\"?", "correct_answer": "Isao Takahata", "incorrect_answers": ["Hayao Miyazaki", "Satoshi Kon", "Sunao Katabuchi"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "What year was \"JoJo's Bizarre Adventure: Phantom Blood\" first released?", "correct_answer": "1987", "incorrect_answers": ["2013", "1983", "1995"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the anime Initial D, how does Takumi Fujiwara describe a drift?", "correct_answer": "'. . . the front tires slide so the car won't face the inside'", "incorrect_answers": ["'. . . the wheels lose traction, making the car slide sideways'", "'. . . the car oversteers through a curve, causing it to turn faster'", "'. . . you turn a lot'"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which one of these characters is from \"Legendz : Tale of the Dragon Kings\"?", "correct_answer": "Shiron", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack", "Axia", "Drum"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the Naruto manga, what is the last name of Tsunade?", "correct_answer": "Senju", "incorrect_answers": ["Haruno", "Uzumaki", "Yamanaka"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which person from \"JoJo's Bizarre Adventure\" does NOT house a reference to a band, artist, or song earlier than 1980?", "correct_answer": "Giorno Giovanna", "incorrect_answers": ["Josuke Higashikata", "Jolyne Cujoh", "Johnny Joestar"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these names are not a character of JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?", "correct_answer": "JoJo Kikasu", "incorrect_answers": ["Jean-Pierre Polnareff", "George Joestar", "Risotto Nero"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Author of the manga Uzumaki?", "correct_answer": "Junji Ito", "incorrect_answers": ["\tNoboru Takahashi", "Akira Toriyama", "Masashi Kishimoto"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio animated \"To Love-Ru\"?", "correct_answer": "Xebec", "incorrect_answers": ["Trigger", "Sunrise", "Kyoto Animation"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann's KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki's \"Monster\"?", "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow", "incorrect_answers": ["What a Wonderful World", "When You Wish Upon A Star", "Singing In The Rain"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which one of these characters is from \"Legendz : Tale of the Dragon Kings\"?", "correct_answer": "Shiron", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack", "Axia", "Drum"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the first episode of Yu-Gi-Oh: Duel Monsters, what book is Seto Kaiba seen reading at Domino High School?", "correct_answer": "Thus Spoke Zarathustra", "incorrect_answers": ["Beyond Good and Evil", "The Republic", "Meditations"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio animated \"Psycho Pass\"?", "correct_answer": "Production I.G", "incorrect_answers": ["Kyoto Animation", "Shaft", "Trigger"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio animated \"Hidamari Sketch\"?", "correct_answer": "Shaft", "incorrect_answers": ["Trigger", "Kyoto Animation", "Production I.G"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "What is the last line muttered in the anime film \"The End of Evangelion\"?", "correct_answer": "\"How disgusting.\"", "incorrect_answers": ["\"Idiot, I won't let you kill me!\"", "\"Nothing.\"", "\"Goddammit, Shinji.\""]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio produced the anime adaptation of \"xxxHolic\"?", "correct_answer": "Production I.G", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Kyoto Animation"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the anime, Full Metal Panic!, who is Kaname's best friend?", "correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa", "incorrect_answers": ["Melissa Mao", "Ren Mikihara", "Teletha \"Tessa\" Testarossa"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Highschool of the Dead\", where did Komuro and Saeko establish to meet after the bus explosion?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Police Station", "incorrect_answers": ["The Center Mall", "Komuro's House", "On The Main Bridge"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the \"Dragon Ball\" franchise, what is the name of Goku's brother?", "correct_answer": "Raditz", "incorrect_answers": ["Gohan", "Vegeta", "Bardock"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the anime Initial D, how does Takumi Fujiwara describe a drift?", "correct_answer": "'. . . the front tires slide so the car won't face the inside'", "incorrect_answers": ["'. . . the wheels lose traction, making the car slide sideways'", "'. . . the car oversteers through a curve, causing it to turn faster'", "'. . . you turn a lot'"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Director of the 1988 Anime film \"Grave of the Fireflies\"?", "correct_answer": "Isao Takahata", "incorrect_answers": ["Hayao Miyazaki", "Satoshi Kon", "Sunao Katabuchi"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In which manga did the \"404 Girl\" from 4chan originate from?", "correct_answer": "Yotsuba&!", "incorrect_answers": ["Azumanga Daioh", "Lucky Star", "Clover"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In what year did the manga \"Ping Pong\" begin serialization?", "correct_answer": "1996", "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2010", "2003"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio produced \"Sword Art Online\"?", "correct_answer": "A-1 Pictures", "incorrect_answers": ["Production I.G", "Silver Link", "Kyoto Animation"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who is the horror manga artist who made Uzumaki?", "correct_answer": "Junji Ito", "incorrect_answers": ["Kazuo Umezu", "Shintaro Kago", "Sui Ishida"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these anime have over 7,500 episodes?", "correct_answer": "Sazae-san", "incorrect_answers": ["Naruto", "One Piece", "Chibi Maruko-chan"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio produced \"Log Horizon\"?", "correct_answer": "Satelite", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Production I.G"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these names are not a character of JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?", "correct_answer": "JoJo Kikasu", "incorrect_answers": ["Jean-Pierre Polnareff", "George Joestar", "Risotto Nero"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Jewelpet Sunshine\", what is the song that plays when Kanon and her friends bust out of prison?", "correct_answer": "I Don't Want to Miss a Thing", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye Of The Tiger", "Born to be Wild", "Ruby Ring"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of the following countries does \"JoJo's Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders\" not take place in?", "correct_answer": "Philippines", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Pakistan", "Egypt"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these names are not a character of JoJo's Bizarre Adventure?", "correct_answer": "JoJo Kikasu", "incorrect_answers": ["Jean-Pierre Polnareff", "George Joestar", "Risotto Nero"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who is the horror manga artist who made Uzumaki?", "correct_answer": "Junji Ito", "incorrect_answers": ["Kazuo Umezu", "Shintaro Kago", "Sui Ishida"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann's KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki's \"Monster\"?", "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow", "incorrect_answers": ["What a Wonderful World", "When You Wish Upon A Star", "Singing In The Rain"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the first episode of Yu-Gi-Oh: Duel Monsters, what book is Seto Kaiba seen reading at Domino High School?", "correct_answer": "Thus Spoke Zarathustra", "incorrect_answers": ["Beyond Good and Evil", "The Republic", "Meditations"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Director of the 1988 Anime film \"Grave of the Fireflies\"?", "correct_answer": "Isao Takahata", "incorrect_answers": ["Hayao Miyazaki", "Satoshi Kon", "Sunao Katabuchi"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"One Piece\", who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?", "correct_answer": "Edward \"Whitebeard\" Newgate", "incorrect_answers": ["Former Marine Fleet Admiral Sengoku", "Pirate King Gol D Roger", "Silvers Rayleigh"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the anime, Full Metal Panic!, who is Kaname's best friend?", "correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa", "incorrect_answers": ["Melissa Mao", "Ren Mikihara", "Teletha \"Tessa\" Testarossa"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Jewelpet Sunshine\", what is the song that plays when Kanon and her friends bust out of prison?", "correct_answer": "I Don't Want to Miss a Thing", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye Of The Tiger", "Born to be Wild", "Ruby Ring"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Akatsuki's subclass in \"Log Horizon\" is what?", "correct_answer": " Tracker", "incorrect_answers": ["Assassin", "Scribe", "Apprentice"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these anime have over 7,500 episodes?", "correct_answer": "Sazae-san", "incorrect_answers": ["Naruto", "One Piece", "Chibi Maruko-chan"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "What is the name of the school in the anime and manga \"Gosick\"?", "correct_answer": "St. Marguerite", "incorrect_answers": ["St. Augustine", "St. Mary", "St. Bernadette"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio animated \"To Love-Ru\"?", "correct_answer": "Xebec", "incorrect_answers": ["Trigger", "Sunrise", "Kyoto Animation"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "\"Silhouette\", a song performed by the group 'KANA-BOON' is featured as the sixteenth opening of which anime?", "correct_answer": "Naruto: Shippūden", "incorrect_answers": ["One Piece", "Naruto", "Gurren Lagann"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio produced \"Log Horizon\"?", "correct_answer": "Satelite", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunrise", "Xebec", "Production I.G"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Highschool of the Dead\", where did Komuro and Saeko establish to meet after the bus explosion?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Police Station", "incorrect_answers": ["The Center Mall", "Komuro's House", "On The Main Bridge"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who is One Punch Man voiced by in the Japanese version.", "correct_answer": "Makoto Furukawa", "incorrect_answers": ["Zach Aguilar", "Kaito Ishikawa", "Max Mittelman "]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "The \"To Love-Ru\" Manga was started in what year?", "correct_answer": "2006", "incorrect_answers": ["2007", "2004", "2005"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In what year did the manga \"Ping Pong\" begin serialization?", "correct_answer": "1996", "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2010", "2003"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the Overlord Anime who was Cocytus made by?", "correct_answer": "Warrior Takemikazuchi", "incorrect_answers": ["Peroroncino", "Ulbert Alain Odle", "Bukubukuchagama"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio animated \"Hidamari Sketch\"?", "correct_answer": "Shaft", "incorrect_answers": ["Trigger", "Kyoto Animation", "Production I.G"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who is the horror manga artist who made Uzumaki?", "correct_answer": "Junji Ito", "incorrect_answers": ["Kazuo Umezu", "Shintaro Kago", "Sui Ishida"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Medaka Kurokami from \"Medaka Box\" has what abnormality?", "correct_answer": "The End", "incorrect_answers": ["Perfection", "Sandbox", "Fairness"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which person from \"JoJo's Bizarre Adventure\" does NOT house a reference to a band, artist, or song earlier than 1980?", "correct_answer": "Giorno Giovanna", "incorrect_answers": ["Josuke Higashikata", "Jolyne Cujoh", "Johnny Joestar"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the anime, Full Metal Panic!, who is Kaname's best friend?", "correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa", "incorrect_answers": ["Melissa Mao", "Ren Mikihara", "Teletha \"Tessa\" Testarossa"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which studio animated Afro Samurai?", "correct_answer": "Gonzo", "incorrect_answers": ["Kyoto Animation", "xebec", "Production I.G"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann's KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki's \"Monster\"?", "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow", "incorrect_answers": ["What a Wonderful World", "When You Wish Upon A Star", "Singing In The Rain"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the Naruto manga, what is the last name of Tsunade?", "correct_answer": "Senju", "incorrect_answers": ["Haruno", "Uzumaki", "Yamanaka"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the Overlord Anime who was Cocytus made by?", "correct_answer": "Warrior Takemikazuchi", "incorrect_answers": ["Peroroncino", "Ulbert Alain Odle", "Bukubukuchagama"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which animation studio produced \"Sword Art Online\"?", "correct_answer": "A-1 Pictures", "incorrect_answers": ["Production I.G", "Silver Link", "Kyoto Animation"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Highschool of the Dead\", where did Komuro and Saeko establish to meet after the bus explosion?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Police Station", "incorrect_answers": ["The Center Mall", "Komuro's House", "On The Main Bridge"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"Jewelpet Sunshine\", what is the song that plays when Kanon and her friends bust out of prison?", "correct_answer": "I Don't Want to Miss a Thing", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye Of The Tiger", "Born to be Wild", "Ruby Ring"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"One Piece\", who is the girl who overcame her enslaved past and became an agent of an army to fight the corrupt government?", "correct_answer": "Koala", "incorrect_answers": ["Boa Hancock", "Nico Robin", "Emporio Ivankov "]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In \"One Piece\", who confirms the existence of the legendary treasure, One Piece?", "correct_answer": "Edward \"Whitebeard\" Newgate", "incorrect_answers": ["Former Marine Fleet Admiral Sengoku", "Pirate King Gol D Roger", "Silvers Rayleigh"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "What year was \"JoJo's Bizarre Adventure: Phantom Blood\" first released?", "correct_answer": "1987", "incorrect_answers": ["2013", "1983", "1995"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Author of the manga Uzumaki?", "correct_answer": "Junji Ito", "incorrect_answers": ["\tNoboru Takahashi", "Akira Toriyama", "Masashi Kishimoto"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the anime Initial D, how does Takumi Fujiwara describe a drift?", "correct_answer": "'. . . the front tires slide so the car won't face the inside'", "incorrect_answers": ["'. . . the wheels lose traction, making the car slide sideways'", "'. . . the car oversteers through a curve, causing it to turn faster'", "'. . . you turn a lot'"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who is One Punch Man voiced by in the Japanese version.", "correct_answer": "Makoto Furukawa", "incorrect_answers": ["Zach Aguilar", "Kaito Ishikawa", "Max Mittelman "]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "In the \"Dragon Ball\" franchise, what is the name of Goku's brother?", "correct_answer": "Raditz", "incorrect_answers": ["Gohan", "Vegeta", "Bardock"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Which of these anime have over 7,500 episodes?", "correct_answer": "Sazae-san", "incorrect_answers": ["Naruto", "One Piece", "Chibi Maruko-chan"]}
{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Who was the Director of the 1988 Anime film \"Grave of the Fireflies\"?", "correct_answer": "Isao Takahata", "incorrect_answers": ["Hayao Miyazaki", "Satoshi Kon", "Sunao Katabuchi"]}
